bodhost.com 2006-11-13

# :: Welcome ::

|  | 

Chat live with   
sales and support   
personnel

|   
---|---|---  
| ** Privacy Policy** |   
  
---|---  
  
> This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which BOD Host collects, uses, stores, archives, and discloses information collected from users of this Website. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.
> 
> **The Information We Collect:  
>  **This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the BOD Host website. On some pages you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. We may ask for personal information such as your name, company name, address, phone number, e-mail address, and credit card information.
> 
> **The Way We Use This Information:  
>  **We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
> 
> We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. We will use information stored in our database about you to provide support. Email addresses and other data collected in support requests are not shared with outside parties unless you have consented as such to help us provide you with technical support. Bod Host may email promotional offers to Bod Host customers from outside vendors, partners, or suppliers.
> 
> BOD Host uses aggregated, anonymous data for research regarding the effectiveness of BOD Host!|s marketing, advertising, and sales efforts. BOD Host does not use such anonymous information for any other purpose.
> 
> Finally, Bod Host does not share or use customer information in ways unrelated to this policy without providing customers an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated use.
> 
> **Our Commitment To Data Security:  
>  **To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
> 
> **Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:  
>  **Protecting the privacy of minors is important to Bod Host.  Therefore, Bod Host never collects or maintains information our website from customers under the age of 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under the age of 18.
> 
> **How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:  
>  **You can correct factual errors in your personal information by sending us a request with sufficient evidence and instructions. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.  We reserve the right to disclose aggregated, anonymous data to investors and potential partners.
> 
> **How To Contact Us:  
>  **Should you have questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please email your concern to[ privacy@bodhosting.com](mailto:privacy@bodhosting.com)
